sup everyone Sonic the Hedgehog here
Tamers12345 one two three four five was nice
enough to let me upload on of my sweet
Bartleby x Sonic fanfics on his youtube
channel well here we go I hope you enjoy
I can't believe it I I actually got away
with it I got three thousand dollars
this will feed so many poor people hello
my name is Sonic the Hedgehog or as some
people more commonly refer as Robin Hood
you may be wondering why I'm so excited
well the reason for that is because I
was able to steal three thousand dollars
from the richest and sexiest man in the
village if not the entire world Bartleby
Montclair of Dresden I stole from him
once before but barely got away with my
life that time this time though it was
surprisingly easy almost as if it was a
trap no maybe I was just lucky this time
I ran straight to the forest and sat
down behind a tree to take a rest and
think over how good I've done suddenly
though my subs Manic ‘n Sonia ran up to
me Manic Sonia check out all this money
I got finally our friends and family
will be able to eat I said gleefully no
Sonic you've got to run get your smelly
ass is far away from here as you can
Lord Bartleby knows you stole it he's
coming here right now my sister Sonja
said with fear in her eyes you've got to
be kidding me I shouted Lord Bartleby
never goes out to capture thieves in
person he usually sends guards instead
so why now Manic looked at Sonia then to
me actually Sonic we overheard some
guards they said something along the
lines of Bartleby wanting a piece of
that ass we believe he may have been
talking about you bro suddenly two
arrows came out of nowhere and straight
through Manic ‘n Sonia's heads the two
of them fell down in a pool of their own
blood I looked over to see a sexy
muscular man in tights with long blond
hair flowing in the wind behind five
elite guards in front of them were two
of my other friends on their knees with
their hands behind their heads as
prisoners it was Knuckles and Mindy
Sonic help us Knuckles said shaking with
fear please I don't want it at you shut
up [ __ ] it was at this moment that Mindy
realized Manic ‘n Sonja's dead bodies
be
for her oh my God Sony don't let him hem
Kahless that's it silence the [ __ ]
suddenly one of the guards cut off mind
his head oh my God Nicole screamed I've
been waiting for this day my fat Lou
[ __ ] you will do exactly as I say your
other friend will meet the same fate
lowered Bartleby said I am nobody's
[ __ ] especially not the [ __ ] of
someone who killed my brother and sister
I shouted back um so you say if I expect
your ass with great force you wouldn't
like it the sexy man asked I blushed not
no well maybe a little but that doesn't
mean I see my blushing you must like
that [ __ ] well I guess I'll make your
dream a reality God go catch a knife at
lubitsch make sure to keep him alive so
I can bang his ex Bartleby said as he
swiftly and majestically pulled out his
rapier from its sheath and stabbed
Knuckles through the heart killing him
instantly I took off running the guards
immediately followed so this is why it
was so easy to steal from Bartleby it
really was a trap he purposely let me
steal the money so he could follow me
and bang me in the ass I pull to my bow
stopped and aimed five arrows in the
direction of the guards I shot all five
arrows in one shot I killed all of them
suddenly Bartleby came running out from
behind a tree I tried shooting arrows at
him but he dodged every single one of
them like a boss and began running
towards me I ran out of arrows so I
dropped the bow and took of running in
front of my I saw a cave hidden behind a
bunch of plants and vines I jumped in I
backed up into the corner of the cave
shaking in fear suddenly Bartleby tried
breaking into the cave but thanks to the
plants he got all tangled up
specifically his tights they got stuck
on a bunch of twigs they ripped a little
bit leaving Bartleby's big plump butt
completely exposed it looked so juicy I
blushed and licked my lips I'll be there
soon bitch hehehe he said I whimpered
and fear and backed up even further stay
away from me I cried make me thankfully
he was happened trouble
it seemed like the more he struggled the
more tangled up he got ha can't get in
can you I said we'll see about that much
suddenly he ripped off his pants no I
thought to myself since the only trouble
Bartleby was really having was the twigs
getting stuck to his pants it seemed to
be an easy task getting free you're
about to become my [ __ ] Bartleby was in
the cave Bartleby jumping on top of me
and began to rape me my eyes filled with
tears I thought the rape would hurt but
it felt lovely Varl teddy I love you I
love you to my Beach I love you too with
fat bear lobby kissed my forehead and we
fell aSleet in the cave the end